Last Updated on 28th July 2019



Education

Dalian Univ. of Technology

«««< HEAD B.Eng. in Computer Science

===== B.E. in Computer

Science »»»>

2016.09-2020.06

Links

Blog:// blog.fuujiro.com Github://@fuujiro LinkedIn:// fuujiro

Introduction

«««< HEAD

Apply: Research Intern

I love programming Familiar with C/C++ language Understand and use Linux/Unix systems Comprehend Computer **Graphics** and Vision passionate about open source projects Hope to be a intern at HKU CS Dept.

Apply: Software Development Engineer

I love programming Familiar with **C/C++** language Understand and use Linux/Unix systems Comprehend Redis and database principles passionate about open source projects Hope to be a good software engineer »»»>

Skills

Programming

Programming Language C++ • C • Python • LTEX Operating System Linux/Unix • Shell • Vim Database Redis • SQL

Language

native Mandarin fluent English

Projects

JiroOS A toy Operating System 2019.3

- X86-based tiny operating system, supported physical machines and virtual machine
- Implement segment/page memory allocation, process thread management, synchronous asynchronous mutual exclusion, I/O process communication and file

e312df501bac47a0bd59885e0ed17540087a0d35
• Referring to other open source implementations, 64-bit extensions and ARM

Socket Unix Networking Programming / socket / Chatting room 2018.12

- Implement TCP/UDP socket network Programming
- IO multiplexing with select/poll/epoll model
- Develop a Chatting room based on select model

LIMS Library Information Management System 2017.6

- · With book add, delete, modify & three-way search, Bestseller recommendation function
- · Own administrator & user the two relationship, with account recovery function, color interactive terminal interface
- LIMS has 42 stars in GitHub, which becomes one of the most popular Library **Information Management System**^{C tag} projects

Experience

National Undergraduate Training Programs for Innovation and Entrepreneurship Undergraduate Research in Robotic Calibration

2018.01 - Present | Dalian, China

- Research on Robot Arm Calibration Based on Zhengyou-Zhang Calibration Algorithm
- Try the new calibration board marked by ARUco, optimize the original calibration algorithm
- · Our DUT-RVLab update research progress on GitHub

Cardiff University, UK Big Data & HPC Summer School

2018.07 - 2018.08 | Cardiff, UK

- · Participate in a school-funded summer exchange program with School of Engneering, Cardiff University
- · Learn about big data, machine learning and high performance computing
- · Successfully completed the final Hackathon closing project, implementing a demo e312df501bac47a0bd59885e0ed1754008 fagets are recognition

"WeGeek" WeChat Mini Program hackathon "Time Cross" Mini Program 2018.12 | Beijing, China

- · Participate in the WeChat Mini Program hackathon jointly organized by Segmentfault and WeChat
- Developed a mini program that tried to replace the **Tencent Document**

Awards

2018	1st Prize	Liaoning Computer Multimedia Design Competition + Scholarship
2018	2nd Prize	The 8th APMCM Asia Pacific Mathematical Modeling Competition in 2018
2017	1st Prize	2017 Ti Cup Electronic Design Competition of Dalian Univ. of Tech.
2017	2nd Prize	The 26th Dalian Mathematics Competition in University Student